2/21/22, 8:19 PM Akshay Resume



Akshay Pawar

Web Developer & Backend Developer

About Me

Hello! I'm Akshay Pawar.i am fullstack developer with 4 + years of experience, using .net technology with various version and desing patter like as MVC, i have knowledge of WEB API and Desktop Application as well.i am working with various domain like healthcare, education, ERP. i am working with payment getway and reporting tools

Age

29

Email

pawarakshay09@gmail.com

Phone

+91 9156016706

Address

Pune

Professional Skills

ASP.NET

MVC

MSSQL

WEB API

ASP.NET Core

Entity FrameWork

Work Experience

Web Developer at Prism

Aug, 2017 - Present

Leverage agile frameworks to provide a robust synopsis for high level overviews. Iterative approaches to corporate strategy foster collaborative thinking to further the overall value proposition.

Web Developer at Paramount

June, 2013 - May, 2015

Override the digital divide with additional clickthroughs from DevOps. Nanotechnology immersion along the information highway will close the loop on focusing solely on the bottom line.

Junior Web Developer at P&G group

Jan, 2011 - May, 2013

User generated content in real-time will have multiple touchpoints for offshoring. Organically grow the holistic world view of disruptive innovation via workplace diversity and empowerment.

Project's

Web Developer at Prism

Aug, 2017 - Present

Leverage agile frameworks to provide a robust synopsis for high level overviews. Iterative approaches to corporate strategy foster collaborative thinking to further the overall value proposition.

Web Developer at Paramount

June, 2013 - May, 2015

Override the digital divide with additional clickthroughs from DevOps. Nanotechnology immersion along the information highway will close the loop on focusing solely on the bottom line. 2/21/22, 8:19 PM Akshay Resume

Junior Web Developer at P&G group

Jan, 2011 - May, 2013

User generated content in real-time will have multiple touchpoints for offshoring. Organically grow the holistic world view of disruptive innovation via workplace diversity and empowerment.

Education

Masters in Computer Science from Pune University

2014 - 2017

Leverage agile frameworks to provide a robust synopsis for high level overviews. Iterative approaches to corporate strategy foster collaborative thinking to further the overall value proposition.

Bachelor of Computer Science from Pune University

2011 - 2014

Override the digital divide with additional clickthroughs from DevOps. Nanotechnology immersion along the information highway will close the loop on focusing solely on the bottom line.

Contact

Address

•

Pune

G

Phone

https://www.facebook.com/templateflip

bhttps://twitter.com/templateflip

+91 9156016706

Email

pawarakshay09@gmail.com

(0)

https://www.instagram.com/templateflip

https://github.com/templateflip